<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string-array name="movie_array">
        <item>@string-array/tt1475582</item>
        <item>@string-array/tt0087182</item>
        <item>@string-array/tt0088847</item>
        <item>@string-array/tt0090060</item>
        <item>@string-array/tt0104868</item>
        <item>@string-array/tt0105946</item>
        <item>@string-array/tt0108052</item>
        <item>@string-array/tt0111282</item>
        <item>@string-array/tt0119925</item>
        <item>@string-array/tt0129387</item>
        <item>@string-array/tt0249462</item>
        <item>@string-array/tt0457939</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tt1475582">
        <item name="id">tt1475582</item>
        <item name="title">The Third Man</item>
        <item name="year">1949</item>
        <item name="shortPlot">Pulp novelist Holly Martins travels to shadowy</item>
        <item name="fullPlot">Pulp novelist Holly Martins travels to shadowy, postwar Vienna, only to find himself investigating the mysterious death of an old friend, black-market opportunist Harry Lime.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tt0087182">
        <item name="id">tt0087182</item>
        <item name="title">Dune</item>
        <item name="year">1984</item>
        <item name="shortPlot">A Duke's son leads desert warriors against the galactic emperor</item>
        <item name="fullPlot">A Duke's son leads desert warriors against the galactic emperor and his father's evil nemesis when they assassinate his father and free their desert world from the emperor's rule.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tt0088847">
        <item name="id">tt0088847</item>
        <item name="title">The Breakfast Club</item>
        <item name="year">1985</item>
        <item name="shortPlot">Five high school students, all different stereotypes</item>
        <item name="fullPlot">Five high school students, all different stereotypes, meet in detention, where they pour their hearts out to each other, and discover how they have a lot more in common than they thought.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tt0090060">
        <item name="id">tt0090060</item>
        <item name="title">St. Elmo's Fire</item>
        <item name="year">1985</item>
        <item name="shortPlot">A group of friends, just out of college</item>
        <item name="fullPlot">A group of friends, just out of college, struggle with adulthood.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tt0104868">
        <item name="id">tt0104868</item>
        <item name="title">The Mighty</item>
        <item name="year">1998</item>
        <item name="shortPlot">This tells the story of a strong friendship between a young</item>
        <item name="fullPlot">This tells the story of a strong friendship between a young boy with Morquio's syndrome and an older boy who is always bullied because of his size. Adapted from the novel, Freak the Mighty,...</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tt0105946">
        <item name="id">tt0105946</item>
        <item name="title">Babylon-5</item>
        <item name="year">1994–1998</item>
        <item name="shortPlot">A space station in neutral territory is the focus of</item>
        <item name="fullPlot">A space station in neutral territory is the focus of a unique five year saga.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tt0108052">
        <item name="id">tt0108052</item>
        <item name="title">Schlinder's List</item>
        <item name="year">1993</item>
        <item name="shortPlot">In Poland during World War II, Oskar Schindler gradually becomes concerned</item>
        <item name="fullPlot">In Poland during World War II, Oskar Schindler gradually becomes concerned for his Jewish workforce after witnessing their persecution by the Nazis.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tt0111282">
        <item name="id">tt0111282</item>
        <item name="title">Stargate</item>
        <item name="year">1994</item>
        <item name="shortPlot">An interstellar teleportation device, found in Egypt, leads to a planet with humans</item>
        <item name="fullPlot">An interstellar teleportation device, found in Egypt, leads to a planet with humans resembling ancient Egyptians who worship the god Ra.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tt0119925">
        <item name="id">tt0119925</item>
        <item name="title">The Postman</item>
        <item name="year">1997</item>
        <item name="shortPlot">A nameless drifter dons a postman's uniform and bag of mail as he begins</item>
        <item name="fullPlot">A nameless drifter dons a postman's uniform and bag of mail as he begins a quest to inspire hope to the survivors living in post-apocalyptic America.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tt0129387">
        <item name="id">tt0129387</item>
        <item name="title">There's Something About Mary</item>
        <item name="year">1998</item>
        <item name="shortPlot">A man gets a chance to meet up with his dream girl from highschool</item>
        <item name="fullPlot">A man gets a chance to meet up with his dream girl from highschool, even though his date with her back then was a complete disaster.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tt0249462">
        <item name="id">tt0249462</item>
        <item name="title">Billy Elliot</item>
        <item name="year">2000</item>
        <item name="shortPlot">A talented young boy becomes torn between his unexpected love of dance</item>
        <item name="fullPlot">A talented young boy becomes torn between his unexpected love of dance and the disintegration of his family.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="tt0457939">
        <item name="id">tt0457939</item>
        <item name="title">The Holiday</item>
        <item name="year">2006</item>
        <item name="shortPlot">Two women troubled with guy-problems swap homes in each other's countries</item>
        <item name="fullPlot">Two women troubled with guy-problems swap homes in each other's countries, where they each meet a local guy and fall in love.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>